<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jaipur Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="Food">Food</string>
    <string name="Sites">Sites</string>
    <string name="Clubs">Clubs</string>

    <!--
        nRajputana = name
        dRajputana = description
     -->

    <!-- Hotels -->
    <string name="nRajputana">ITC Rajputana</string>
    <string name="dRajputana">
        Set in the city center, this luxe hotel with a lavish lobby is a 7-minute walk from Jaipur
        Junction train station and 3.9 km from the unique Hawa Mahal palace, built to shield royal
        women from the public.
    </string>

    <string name="nRadisson">Radisson Blu</string>
    <string name="dRadisson">
        This upscale hotel is 1.5 km from Jawahar Circle, 2.3 km from Durgapura railway station and
        8 km from Rambagh Palace.
    </string>

    <string name="nRambagh">Taj Rambagh Palace</string>
    <string name="dRambagh">
        In an ornate converted palace dating from 1835, this opulent hotel is 4 km from both
        Gandhinagar Jaipur train station, and art and history exhibits at the Albert Hall Museum.
    </string>

    <string name="nLalit">The Lalit Jaipur</string>
    <string name="dLalit">
        Set 1.6 km from the airport, this high-end hotel with Haveli architecture is 12 km from the
        City Palace complex and the 18th-century Jantar Mantar park.
    </string>

    <string name="nMarriott">Jaipur Marriott</string>
    <string name="dMarriott">
        Set 2.3 km from Durgapura Railway Station, this upscale hotel with a partial glass facade is
        14 minutes walk from Jawahar Circle garden and 11 km from Hawa Mahal palace.
    </string>

    <!-- Food -->
    <string name="nDalBaati">Dal Baati Churma</string>
    <string name="dDalBaati">
        It is a traditional dish with a history that is extraordinary as its taste.It is three in
        one dish that consists of sweet churma, spicy daal, and baati. This combo of ‘Dal Baati
        Churma’ is a wonderful way to warm yourself up on a cold day!
    </string>

    <string name="nKachori">Pyaaz Ki Kachori</string>
    <string name="dKachori">
        This mouthwatering dish from the streets of Jaipur is surely one of the everyday morning
        food items from the Rajasthani cuisine. Steaming hot fiery Pyaaz Ki Kachori with Hot Masala
        Tea is a perfect winter breakfast.
    </string>

    <string name="nGhevar">Ghevar</string>
    <string name="dGhevar">
        A classic Indian dessert served in different variety such as plain, malai and mava. It is a
        disc-shaped sweet cake made with all-purpose flour and soaked in sugar syrup. No Rajasthani
        food is complete without Ghevar.
    </string>

    <string name="nMirchiVada">Mirchi Vada</string>
    <string name="dMirchiVada">
        For all the spicy food lovers Mirchi Vada is your dish. It is a spicy Indian snack
        consisting of chili and potato stuffing, served hot with Tamarind chutney.
    </string>

    <string name="nThali">Rajasthani Thali</string>
    <string name="dThali">
        A full-fledged meal call for a Rajasthani thali. It is an absolute delight to eat a little
        bit of everything from the best that a cuisine can offer.
    </string>

    <!-- Sites -->
    <string name="nHawaMahal">Hawa Mahal</string>
    <string name="dHawaMahal">
        The Hawa Mahal stands at the intersection of the main road in Jaipur, Badi Chaupad. It is
        regarded as the signature building of Jaipur and was built by Maharaja Sawai Pratap Singh.
    </string>

    <string name="nCityPalace">City Palace</string>
    <string name="dCityPalace">
        Located in Jaipur, The City Palace is the main palace from where the Maharaja reigned from.
        The palace includes the Chandra Mahan and Mubarak Mahal along with various other buildings
        within the complex. It is located towards the north-eastern side of Jaipur.
    </string>

    <string name="nAmberFort">Amber Fort</string>
    <string name="dAmberFort">
        Amber Fort, situated 11 kms from Jaipur, is a fort built with great artistic taste. Cradled
        on the top of a hill forming a beautiful reflection in Maotha Lake, it is popularly known as
        Amer Fort.
    </string>

    <string name="nNahargarhFort">Nahargarh Fort</string>
    <string name="dNahargarhFort">
        Nahargarh Fort, situated on the outer skirts of Jaipur is an epitome of great architecture
        and planning. Drenched with rich past, the fort allows you a picturesque view of the entire
        city. Built in 1734, this grand architecture is a perfect way to begin the excursion of this
        pink city.
    </string>

    <string name="nAlbertHall">Albert Hall Museum</string>
    <string name="dAlbertHall">
        Albert Hall Museum is one of the oldest museums of Rajasthan. It has a rich collection of
        various kinds of items such as paintings, carpets, ivory, stone, metal sculptures, colourful
        crystal works etc.
    </string>

    <!--Clubs-->
    <string name="nHOP">House Of People</string>
    <string name="dHOP">
        One of the premium rooftops in Jaipur, House of People has segregated sittings; one can
        enjoy the live music in lounge or can choose to stay on toes with the rock music in pub
        area. This beautiful ambiance attracts ladies for free on every Thursdays.
    </string>

    <string name="nBlackout">Blackout</string>
    <string name="dBlackout">
        As the names hints a place with complete darkness where you find urself life while dancing
        to the beats of music relieving yourself from all the hues of stress.
    </string>

    <string name="nDuplay">Duplay</string>
    <string name="dDuplay">
        Stylish neon-lit nightclub in a hotel with comfortable seating and a large dance floor.
    </string>

    <string name="nFBar">F Bar &amp; Lounge</string>
    <string name="dFBar">
        An ideal destination for Jaipur partygoers which mishmash of all sides of stylish lounge
        including food, drinks, music &amp; experience.  Unwind work and spend nice evening here out
        with your f-avourite people.
    </string>

    <string name="nWTF">WTF Cafe</string>
    <string name="dWTF">
        The unmatchable aura of WTF makes it a must visit place, where reunions could be celebrated
        with chilled beer mugs and delicious choice food.
    </string>

</resources>
